Audrey Beck Papers
© 2005 University of Connecticut
- Series II: House of Representatives, undated, 1959-1978
  - Subseries A: Subject Files, undated, 1959-1978
    - Connecticut Association of Local Legislators (CALL), 1973 (Box 2:, Folder 61)
    - Connecticut Census Data, 1970 (Box 2:, Folder 62)
    - Connecticut Citizen Action Group (CCAG), 1971-1976 (Box 2:, Folder 63)
    - Connecticut Commission on Housing, 1970 (Box 2:, Folder 64)
    - Connecticut Development Commission, 1959-1975 (Box 2:, Folder 65)
    - Connecticut Facts, 1968-1974 (Box 2:, Folder 66)
    - Connecticut Finances, 1971 (Box 2:, Folder 67)
    - Connecticut Hospital Association, 1970-1973 (Box 3:, Folder 68)
    - Connecticut Housing, 1960-1970 (Box 3:, Folder 69)
    - Connecticut in Focus, 1970 (Box 3:, Folder 70)
    - Connecticut Industrial Building Commission, 1972 (Box 3:, Folder 71)
    - Connecticut Interregional Planning Program (CIPP), 1967-1971 (Box 3:, Folder 72)
    - Connecticut Local Government Expenditures & Revenue, 1969 (Box 3:, Folder 73)
    - Connecticut Public Expenditure Council (CPEC), 1960-1965 (Box 3:, Folder 74)
    - Connecticut Regional Planning, 19591-964 (Box 3:, Folder 75)
    - Connecticut State Tax Structure, 1968 (Box 3:, Folder 76)
    - Connecticut Valley Hospital, 1974 (Box 3:, Folder 77)
    - Consultants—kickbacks, 1974 (Box 3:, Folder 78)
    - Corporate offices and industrial parks, 1970-1971 (Box 3:, Folder 79)
    - Corrections, 1968-1974 (Box 3:, Folder 80)
    - Correspondence—Interdepartmental, 1969-1970 (Box 3:, Folder 81)
    - Courts, 1972-1975 (Box 3:, Folder 82)
    - Crime Commission, 1972-1974 (Box 3:, Folder 83)
    - Criminal Justice, 1973-1974 (Box 3:, Folder 84)
    - Daddario, 1970 (Box 3:, Folder 85)
    - Day Care, 1971-1974 (Box 3:, Folder 86)
    - Deaf, 1967 (Box 3:, Folder 87)
    - Demand deposits, 1969-1971 (Box 3:, Folder 88)
    - Democratic Platform and Legislative Scoreboard, 1972 (Box 3:, Folder 89)
    - Dissent on Campus, 1969 (Box 3:, Folder 90)
    - Divorce, 1973 (Box 3:, Folder 91)
    - Drucker: Government—Philosophy and Trends, 1969 (Box 3:, Folder 92)
    - Drugs, 1969-1971 (Box 3:, Folder 93)
    - Eastern States Exposition, 1971 (Box 3:, Folder 94)
    - Eighteen Year Old Vote, 1969 (Box 3:, Folder 95)
    - Elderly Aging, Elderly Aging, 1968-1973 (Box 3:, Folder 96)
    - Employment: Beck, 1966-1974 (Box 3:, Folder 97)
    - Emergency Medical Services (EMS), 1974 (Box 3:, Folder 98)
    - Energy Agency, 1973-1975 (Box 4:, Folder 99)
    - Environmental Protection, Department of (DEP), 1975-1976 (Box 4:, Folder 100)
    - Epileptics, 1969 (Box 4:, Folder 101)
    - Etherington Commission, 1971-1972 (Box 4:, Folder 102)
    - Ethics Bill—Carlson, 1972-1973 (Box 4:, Folder 103)
    - Executive Powers: Nixon, 1973 (Box 4:, Folder 104)
    - Fairfield Hills Hospital, 1973-1975 (Box 4:, Folder 105)
    - Fuel adjustment charge, 1974 (Box 4:, Folder 106)
    - Fuel crisis, 1974 (Box 4:, Folder 107)
    - Gambling, 1968-1975 (Box 4:, Folder 108)
    - Government departments: state, 1969-1971 (Box 4:, Folder 109)
    - Grants: libraries, 1969-1971 (Box 4:, Folder 110)
    - Grasso, Ella: Governor, 1968-1975 (Box 4:, Folder 111)
    - Grasso, Ella: press, 1974 (Box 4:, Folder 112)
    - Grasso, Ella: public statements, 1974 (Box 4:, Folder 113)
    - Gun control, 1968-1973 (Box 4:, Folder 114)
    - Gypsy moth, 1970-1972 (Box 4:, Folder 115)
    - Hartford Process, 1972-1974 (Box 4:, Folder 116)
    - Health Costs, 1972-1973 (Box 4:, Folder 117)
    - Health districts, 1973-1974 (Box 4:, Folder 118)
    - Health manpower, 1972 (Box 4:, Folder 119)
    - Hearing aids, 1969-1973 (Box 4:, Folder 120)
    - Hilsman campaign, 1972 (Box 4:, Folder 121)
    - Hospitals, 1968-1974 (Box 4:, Folder 122)
    - Hospitals, Commission on, 1973 (Box 4:, Folder 123)
    - Housing, 1968-1972 (Box 4:, Folder 124)
    - Housing, 1968-1973 (Box 4:, Folder 125)
    - Housing—Tax abatement, 1971-1972 (Box 4:, Folder 126)
    - Human Resource Grant, 1970-1971 (Box 4:, Folder 127)
    - Human Rights—Blacks, 1969-1975 (Box 4:, Folder 128)
    - Human Rights and Opportunities, 1969-1974 (Box 4:, Folder 129)
    - Humanities Council, 1973 (Box 4:, Folder 130)
    - Hundred Club, 1969 (Box 4:, Folder 131)
    - Insurance, 1971-1972 (Box 4:, Folder 132)
    - Interim planning and zoning, 1969-1970 (Box 4:, Folder 133)
    - Issues: polls, 1972-1974 (Box 4:, Folder 134)
    - Judge selection, 1974-1975 (Box 4:, Folder 135)
    - Justice, Department of, 1972 (Box 4:, Folder 136)
    - Juvenile Court System, 1969-1975 (Box 4:, Folder 137)
    - Kerner Report, 1968-1969 (Box 4:, Folder 138)
    - Labor, 1973-1974 (Box 4:, Folder 139)
    - Labor Department, 1975 (Box 4:, Folder 140)
    - Labor—General Assembly, 1967-1975 (Box 4:, Folder 141)
    - Law libraries, 1969 (Box 4:, Folder 142)
    - Leadership: House, 1972-1974 (Box 4:, Folder 143)
    - Leasing Probe, 1974-1975 (Box 4:, Folder 144)
    - Legislation—Child care, swimming safety, rabies, 1972-1973 (Box 4:, Folder 145)
    - Legislation—Proposed, 1969-1973 (Box 4:, Folder 146)
    - Libraries, 1968-1979 (Box 4:, Folder 147)
    - Libraries: Regional, 1969-1971 (Box 4:, Folder 148)
    - Library Hearing, 1970-1971 (Box 4:, Folder 149)
    - License plates, 1974 (Box 5:, Folder 150)
    - Lobbyists, 1968-1973 (Box 5:, Folder 151)
    - Local Government expenditures, 1959-1963 (Box 5:, Folder 152)
    - Long Lane Reform School, 1972-1974 (Box 5:, Folder 153)
    - Mansfield Road improvements, 1970 (Box 5:, Folder 154)
    - Mansfield Training School, 1973 (Box 5:, Folder 155)
    - Mansfield Training School, 1973-1978 (Box 5:, Folder 156)
    - Mansfield Training School Health Violations, 1977 (Box 5:, Folder 157)
    - Mansfield Training School Voting, 1968-1972 (Box 5:, Folder 158)
    - Marijuana: Legalization, 1973 (Box 5:, Folder 159)
    - Marriage counseling, 1970-1972 (Box 5:, Folder 160)
    - Medicaid, 1968-1969 (Box 5:, Folder 161)
    - Medical society, 1968 (Box 5:, Folder 162)
    - Mental Health, 1965-1973 (Box 5:, Folder 163)
    - Mental Health—Norwich, 1968-1974 (Box 5:, Folder 164)
    - Mental Health—reporter, 1969-1973 (Box 5:, Folder 165)
    - Mental retardation, 1967-1977 (Box 5:, Folder 166)
    - Mental Retardation Office—Project Challenge, 1973 (Box 5:, Folder 167)
    - Meriden School for Boys, 1969-1974 (Box 5:, Folder 168)
    - Merit rating: unemployment compensation, 1969 (Box 5:, Folder 169)
    - “Meskill's failings”: Beck speeches, 1973 (Box 5:, Folder 170)
    - Mobile homes, 1973-1975 (Box 5:, Folder 171)
    - Mobile homes, 1966-1973 (Box 5:, Folder 172)
    - New England River Basins Commission, 1970-1972 (Box 5:, Folder 173)
    - New Haven Hospital Annual report, 1969 (Box 5:, Folder 174)
    - New Haven—redevelopment, 1974 (Box 5:, Folder 175)
    - NLC—Ethics committee, 1973 (Box 5:, Folder 176)
    - Norwalk, 1969 (Box 5:, Folder 177)
    - Nursing homes, 1968-1978 (Box 5:, Folder 178)
    - Organized crime, 1973-1975 (Box 5:, Folder 179)
    - Public Act 490: Chair, 1971-1972 (Box 5:, Folder 180)
    - Public Acts: Summaries, Substitute Bills, 1973 (Box 5:, Folder 181)
    - Phi Beta Kappa, 1972 (Box 5:, Folder 182)
    - Phosphate detergents, 1971-1973 (Box 5:, Folder 183)
    - Physicians: Need in CT, 1968-1970 (Box 5:, Folder 184)
    - Police Academy, 1969, 1973 (Box 5:, Folder 185)
    - Power Facilities Evaluation Council, 1971 (Box 5:, Folder 186)
    - Power Failure Hearing, 1974 (Box 5:, Folder 187)
    - Power rate base, 1974 (Box 5:, Folder 188)
    - Prescription drug advertising, 1974 (Box 5:, Folder 189)
    - President: Direct election, 1969 (Box 5:, Folder 190)
    - Primary, 1969-1974 (Box 5:, Folder 191)
    - Probate Court Reform, 1969 (Box 5:, Folder 192)
    - Probate Laws Revision, 1969 (Box 5:, Folder 193)
    - Public Utilities Commission (PUC)—Ads, 1974 (Box 5:, Folder 194)
    - Public Utilities Commission (PUC)—Selection method, 1973-1974 (Box 5:, Folder 195)
    - Public Works, 1971 (Box 5:, Folder 195)
    - Ratchford-Bailey: McLoughlin, 1968-1969 (Box 5:, Folder 197)
    - Regional Department of Health, 1974 (Box 5:, Folder 198)
    - Regional planning, 1968-1973 (Box 5:, Folder 199)
    - Rehabilitation, 1966-1969 (Box 6:, Folder 200)
    - Restaurant inspection, 1970 (Box 6:, Folder 201)
    - Retirement and survivorship benefits, 1969 (Box 6:, Folder 202)
    - Riot and incitement to riot, 1969 (Box 6:, Folder 203)
    - Rules committee, 1973-1974 (Box 6:, Folder 204)
    - Seaports, 1970 (Box 6:, Folder 205)
    - Serrano vs. Priest: Disparities in school revenue, 1971 (Box 6:, Folder 206)
    - Session accomplishments, 1973 (Box 6:, Folder 207)
    - Small town coordinators, 1968-1970 (Box 6:, Folder 208)
    - Snowmobile, 1971-1976 (Box 6:, Folder 209)
    - Social Agency, undated (Box 6:, Folder 210)
    - Somers Prison, 1973 (Box 6:, Folder 211)
    - Southern New England Telephone, undated (Box 6:, Folder 212)
    - State Aid to Education, 1970-1973 (Box 6:, Folder 213)
    - State and Urban Development (SUD) Bill Record, undated (Box 6:, Folder 214)
    - State Development: Interim Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 6:, Folder 215)
    - Telegrams and special session, 1969 (Box 6:, Folder 216)
    - Treasurer, 1971-1974 (Box 6:, Folder 217)
    - Truth in lending, 1968 (Box 6:, Folder 218)
    - Unemployment compensation, 1970-1974 (Box 6:, Folder 219)
    - Uniform Consumer Credit Code, 1969 (Box 6:, Folder 220)
    - Unit pricing, 1973 (Box 6:, Folder 221)
    - United Auto Workers (UAW), 1973 (Box 6:, Folder 222)
    - Veterans, 1972-1973 (Box 6:, Folder 223)
    - Voluntown Farm CNVA, 1974 (Box 6:, Folder 224)
    - Votes taken: CT Senate, 1973 (Box 6:, Folder 225)
    - Voting record: House, 1973 (Box 6:, Folder 226)
    - Welfare, 1970-1974 (Box 6:, Folder 227)
    - Welfare, 1965-1969 (Box 6:, Folder 228)
    - Welfare—Guaranteed income, 1970-1973 (Box 6:, Folder 229)
    - Welfare receipts, 1974 (Box 6:, Folder 230)
    - Welfare rents, 1974 (Box 6:, Folder 231)
    - Wiretap, 19970-1973 (Box 6:, Folder 232)
  - Subseries B: Budget, undated, 1948-1975
    - Assessors: IPS (Institute of Public Service), 1970 (Box 6:, Folder 233)
    - Budget, 1975 (Box 6:, Folder 234)
    - Budget, 1969-1972 (Box 6:, Folder 235)
    - Budget, 1971 (Box 6:, Folder 236)
    - Budget deficit, 1974-1975 (Box 6:, Folder 237)
    - Budget—Tax—Zaiman, 1968-1970 (Box 6:, Folder 238)
    - Built in stabilizers, 1948-1961 (Box 6:, Folder 239)
    - Cigarette and liquor, 1972 (Box 6:, Folder 240)
    - Circuit breaker, 1973-1974 (Box 6:, Folder 241)
    - Connecticut, Committee of Correspondence, 1969 (Box 6:, Folder 242)
    - Connecticut Conference of Mayors, 1969-1975 (Box 6:, Folder 243)
    - Connecticut Development Commission, 1959-1968 (Box 6:, Folder 244)
    - Deficit: Causes, Democrats, 1968-1970 (Box 6:, Folder 245)
    - Democratic House: Budget and taxes, 1969 (Box 6:, Folder 246)
    - Elderly Refund, 1967-1971 (Box 6:, Folder 247)
    - Federal Aid to Connecticut, 1968-1975 (Box 6:, Folder 248)
    - Federal and State Grants, 1971 (Box 6:, Folder 249)
    - Federal Reserve, 1966-1967 (Box 6:, Folder 250)
    - Grants, 1969-1974 (Box 6:, Folder 251)
    - Grants—Criminal Administration, 1972 (Box 6:, Folder 252)
    - Grants—DCA Study, 1971 (Box 6:, Folder 253)
    - Grants—Economic Opportunity Act, 1965 (Box 6:, Folder 254)
    - Grants—Health, 1972 (Box 6:, Folder 255)
    - Inventory Tax, 1971 (Box 6:, Folder 256)
    - Investments—Trust Funds, 1971-1974 (Box 6:, Folder 257)
    - Land Tax Idea, undated (Box 6:, Folder 258)
    - Lottery, 1968-1972 (Box 6:, Folder 259)
    - Mansfield: Money impact, including growth grant, 1965-1971 (Box 6:, Folder 260)
    - Mansfield revenues ADM, 1969-1973 (Box 6:, Folder 261)
    - Mansfield Middle School Proposal, 1967 (Box 6:, Folder 262)
    - PPBS, 1969 (Box 6:, Folder 263)
    - Property tax, 1974-1975 (Box 6:, Folder 264)
    - Property tax, 1970-1973 (Box 6:, Folder 265)
    - Property tax credit: roll, 1970 (Box 6:, Folder 266)
    - Property taxes: regional, 1970 (Box 6:, Folder 267)
    - Public pensions, 1968-1973 (Box 6:, Folder 268)
    - Real Estate Conveyance Tax, 1972 (Box 6:, Folder 269)
    - Real Estate: Public Act 490, 1963-1969 (Box 6:, Folder 270)
    - Revenue Sharing, 1972-1973 (Box 6:, Folder 271)
    - Revenue Sharing, 1972-1973 (Box 7:, Folder 272)
    - Revenue Sharing, 1973-1974 (Box 7:, Folder 273)
    - Road Grant, 1967-1971 (Box 7:, Folder 274)
    - Sales Tax collection, 1973 (Box 7:, Folder 275)
    - State Aid: Education, 1970-1971 (Box 7:, Folder 276)
    - State and Local Fiscal Educational crisis, 1969-1973 (Box 7:, Folder 277)
    - State Tax collections, 1968-1972 (Box 7:, Folder 278)
    - State Tax Collections in selected areas: U.S. Census, 1972 (Box 7:, Folder 279)
    - Sullivan Study: local state spending, 1968-1969 (Box 7:, Folder 280)
    - Surplus: State budget, 1970-1975 (Box 7:, Folder 281)
    - Tax and appropriations, 1971-1972 (Box 7:, Folder 282)
    - Tax and budget, 1969 (Box 7:, Folder 283)
    - Tax changes since 1936 in CT, 1968 (Box 7:, Folder 284)
    - Tax clippings, 1968-1979 (Box 7:, Folder 285)
    - Tax increases—IPS, 1965-1968 (Box 7:, Folder 286)
    - Tax on oysters, 1969 (Box 7:, Folder 287)
    - Tax reform commission, 1972-1973 (Box 7:, Folder 288)
    - Tax Task Force, 1970 235 (Box 7:, Folder 289)
    - Taxes, 1972 (Box 7:, Folder 290)
    - Taxes: ACIR Studies (Advisory Commission on Intergovernmental Relations), 1965-1968 (Box 7:, Folder 291)
    - Taxes: League of Women Voters, 1970 (Box 7:, Folder 292)
  - Subseries C: Colleagues, 1967-1977
    - Architect hiring, 1974 (Box 7:, Folder 293)
    - Athanson, George, 1970-1973 (Box 7:, Folder 294)
    - Berry, Louise, 1973-1974 (Box 7:, Folder 295)
    - Biebel, Fred, 1973 (Box 7:, Folder 296)
    - Blumenthal, Morton, 1973 (Box 7:, Folder 297)
    - Candidates: General Assembly, State and Nation, 1968 (Box 7:, Folder 298)
    - Dempsey, John, 1970-1974 (Box 7:, Folder 299)
    - Dunn, Barbara, 1971-1973 (Box 7:, Folder 300)
    - Gill, Joseph, 1975 (Box 7:, Folder 301)
    - Goodwin, Dorothy, 1975 (Box 7:, Folder 302)
    - Gubernatorial discussions, 1974 (Box 7:, Folder 303)
    - Gunther, George, 1974 (Box 7:, Folder 304)
    - Houley, Robert, 1968-1975 (Box 7:, Folder 305)
    - Kennelly, James, 1974 (Box 7:, Folder 306)
    - La Rosa, Paul, 1970 (Box 7:, Folder 307)
    - Lieberman, Joseph, 1973 (Box 7:, Folder 308)
    - Lufkin, Dan, 1974 (Box 7:, Folder 309)
    - Mazzola, Alan, 1973-1974 (Box 7:, Folder 310)
    - Merchant, John, 1970 (Box 7:, Folder 311)
    - Meskill, Thomas, 1973-1974 (Box 7:, Folder 312)
    - Morris, Bruce, 1969-1974 (Box 7:, Folder 313)
    - Morrison, John, 1975-1977 (Box 7:, Folder 314)
    - Nevas, Alan, 1972 (Box 7:, Folder 315)
    - O'Neill, William, 1967-1970 (Box 7:, Folder 316)
    - Ostro, Justin, 1973 (Box 7:, Folder 317)
    - Politicians—State, 1968-1974 (Box 7:, Folder 318)
    - Ratchford, William, 1969-1972 (Box 7:, Folder 319)
    - Ribicoff, Abraham, 1973-1974 (Box 7:, Folder 320)
    - Russell, Maria, 1971 (Box 7:, Folder 321)
    - Schaffer, Gloria, 1971-1974 (Box 7:, Folder 322)
    - State Politicians, 1970-1975 (Box 7:, Folder 323)
    - Stolberg, Irving, 1970-1973 (Box 7:, Folder 324)
    - Tarcauanu, Carol, undated (Box 7:, Folder 325)
    - Wexler, Anne, 1973 (Box 7:, Folder 326)
  - Subseries D: Economy, undated, 1954-1978
    - American economy, 1970-1973 (Box 7:, Folder 327)
    - Carter's Economic Team, 1976 (Box 7:, Folder 328)
    - CBT Newsletter, 1974-1977 (Box 7:, Folder 329)
    - Cities: Economy—CT, Ribicoff, 1971 (Box 7:, Folder 330)
    - Commerce, Department of, 1978 (Box 7:, Folder 331)
    - Connecticut Bureau of Labor Statistics, 1972-1973 (Box 7:, Folder 332)
    - Connecticut Bureau of Labor Statistics, 1974-1977 (Box 7:, Folder 333)
    - Connecticut Conversion, 1971-1973 (Box 7:, Folder 334)
    - Connecticut Development Commission—Economic Profile, 1968-1973 (Box 7:, Folder 335)
    - Connecticut Development News, 1970-1973 (Box 8:, Folder 336)
    - Connecticut Economy: Metropolitan Government, 1967 (Box 8:, Folder 337)
    - Connecticut Industry, 1971-1975 (Box 8:, Folder 338)
    - Connecticut Industries, 1971 (Box 8:, Folder 339)
    - Connecticut Jobs, 1971-1975 (Box 8:, Folder 340)
    - Connecticut Living—rating, 1972-1975 (Box 8:, Folder 341)
    - Council of Economic Advisors, 1972-1978 (Box 8:, Folder 342)
    - Current philosophy—political, 1973-1974 (Box 8:, Folder 343)
    - Development, suburbs (clippings), 1969-1974 (Box 8:, Folder 344)
    - Economics: current philosophy, 1969-1976 (Box 8:, Folder 345)
    - Economy
      - Beck speeches, 1973 (Box 8:, Folder 346)
      - Driscoll, 1973 (Box 8:, Folder 347)
      - Stafford Springs, 1973 (Box 8:, Folder 348)
      - Subcommittee on, 1971-1972 (Box 8:, Folder 349)
      - Subcommittee on, 1971-1972 (Box 8:, Folder 350)
      - Weekly earnings, 1966-1973 (Box 8:, Folder 351)
    - Economy and manpower, 1970-1974 (Box 8:, Folder 352)
    - Employment—Connecticut firms, 1971-1974 (Box 8:, Folder 353)
    - Employment legislation, 1972 (Box 8:, Folder 354)
    - Employment projections—Pinsky, 1972-1975 (Box 8:, Folder 355)
    - Greenwich—Xerox, 1973-1974 (Box 8:, Folder 356)
    - Income differences, 1974-1976 (Box 8:, Folder 357)
    - Industry bonds, undated (Box 8:, Folder 358)
    - Industry location, 1976 (Box 8:, Folder 359)
    - Inflation, 1974-1975 (Box 8:, Folder 360)
    - Jetport, 1969-1973 (Box 8:, Folder 361)
    - Jobs: CT, 1972-1976 (Box 8:, Folder 362)
    - Labor Bulletin, 1969-1973 (Box 8:, Folder 363)
    - Labor Department newsletters, 1971-1974 (Box 8:, Folder 364)
    - Labor Department Statistics, 1972 (Box 8:, Folder 365)
    - Labor New England Industrial Change, 1954 (Box 8:, Folder 366)
    - Land Use: State wide plans, 1973-1974 (Box 8:, Folder 367)
    - Long Island Sound, 1969 (Box 8:, Folder 368)
    - Manpower Training, 1970-1974 (Box 8:, Folder 369)
    - New England Economic Project, 1973-1975 (Box 8:, Folder 370)
    - New England Economy, 1968-1974 (Box 8:, Folder 371)
    - Stamford, 1973-1974 (Box 8:, Folder 372)
    - State Developmental Legislation, 1971-1972 (Box 8:, Folder 373)
    - Trade, 1968-1973 (Box 8:, Folder 374)
    - U.S. Department of Commerce, 1971-1975 (Box 8:, Folder 375)
    - Zoning (clippings), 1970-1975 (Box 8:, Folder 376)
  - Subseries E: Environment, 1967-1975
    - Clean Water Act of 1967 (Box 8:, Folder 377)
    - Environment, 1970-1975 (Box 8:, Folder 378-379)
    - Environment: Joe Gill, 1967-1970 (Box 9:, Folder 380)
    - Environment Department, 1971-1972 (Box 9:, Folder 381)
    - Environmental Policy Act, 1972 (Box 9:, Folder 382)
    - Natural Resources, 1968-1975 (Box 9:, Folder 383)
    - Power and Environment, 1972-1975 (Box 9:, Folder 384)
    - Solid waste, 1968-1973 (Box 9:, Folder 385)
    - Water pollution progress, 1969-1970 (Box 9:, Folder 386)
    - Wetlands, 1969-1973 (Box 9:, Folder 387)
  - Subseries F: Income Tax and Finance, 1960-1978
    - Connecticut's Finances—League of Women Voters, 1969-1970 (Box 9:, Folder 388)
    - Finance, 1960-1978 (Box 9:, Folder 389)
    - Fiscal notes—Grasso campaign, 1974 (Box 9:, Folder 390)
    - Income Tax, 1968-1969 (Box 9:, Folder 391)
    - Income Tax, 1969 (Box 9:, Folder 392)
    - Income Tax, 1970-1971 (Box 9:, Folder 393)
    - Income Tax, 1971 (Box 9:, Folder 394-395)
    - Income Tax
      - Chamber of Commerce, 1969 (Box 9:, Folder 396)
      - Driscoll: Reform, 1968-1969 (Box 9:, Folder 397)
      - Editorials, 1969 (Box 9:, Folder 398)
      - Goodwin, Dorothy, 1969 (Box 9:, Folder 399)
      - Hearing, 1967 (Box 9:, Folder 400)
      - Hughes, New York Times, 1969 (Box 9:, Folder 401)
      - Labor, 1969 (Box 9:, Folder 402)
      - Mail—Negative, 1969 (Box 9:, Folder 403)
      - Michigan, 1967 (Box 9:, Folder 404)
      - Republican Forum, undated (Box 9:, Folder 405)
      - Revenue, 1969 (Box 9:, Folder 406)
      - Seminar, 1969 (Box 9:, Folder 407)
      - Studies: Sazama (Prof. of Economics), 1969 (Box 9:, Folder 408)
      - Tax proposals, 1969 (Box 9:, Folder 409)
    - Kogan: local taxes, 1969-1970 (Box 9:, Folder 410)
    - Organization of State Social Workers Income Tax, 1969 (Box 9:, Folder 411)
    - Taxes, 1961-1973 (Box 9:, Folder 412)
      - Bills, 1973 (Box 9:, Folder 413)
      - Collectors Association, undated (Box 9:, Folder 414)
      - Laws, 1969 (Box 9:, Folder 415)
      - Meeting, 1970 (Box 9:, Folder 416)
      - Plank—Democrats, undated (Box 9:, Folder 417)
      - Structure, 1967 (Box 9:, Folder 418)
    - Tolland County Resolution, 1969 (Box 9:, Folder 419)
  - Subseries G: Legislature, 1964-1977
    - Annual Sessions, 1969-1972 (Box 9:, Folder 420)
    - Bill drafting, 1968-1969 (Box 9:, Folder 421)
    - Compensation schedules, 1971-1973 (Box 9:, Folder 422)
    - Conflict of interest, 1969-1972 (Box 9:, Folder 423)
    - Eagleton report, 1968 (Box 9:, Folder 424)
    - Facts and issues, 1969-1971 (Box 9:, Folder 425)
    - Fair representation, 1964 (Box 9:, Folder 426)
    - Hearings, 1971 (Box 9:, Folder 427)
    - Internship Program, 1969-1970 (Box 9:, Folder 428)
    - Legislative Information System, 1969 (Box 10:, Folder 429)
    - Legislative Management Committee, 1969-1972 (Box 10:, Folder 430)
    - Legislative publications, 1971, 1973 (Box 10:, Folder 431)
    - Legislative Reform—Staff and Services report, 1969-1972 (Box 10:, Folder 432)
    - Legislative Regulation review, undated (Box 10:, Folder 433)
    - Legislative Trends, 1973 (Box 10:, Folder 434)
    - Legislative trips, 1973-1975 (Box 10:, Folder 435)
    - Legislature Accomplishments, 1969-1972 (Box 10:, Folder 436)
    - Legislature Accomplishments, 1974 (Box 10:, Folder 437)
    - Legislature Composition, 1971-1977 (Box 10:, Folder 438)
    - Legislature facts and issues, 1971-1972 (Box 10:, Folder 439)
    - Legislature fiscal information, 1973-1974 (Box 10:, Folder 440)
    - Legislature procedure, 1971 (Box 10:, Folder 441)
    - Legislatures and urban affairs, 1971 (Box 10:, Folder 442)
    - Reapportionment, 1971-1973 (Box 10:, Folder 443)
    - Reform—General, 1970-1973 (Box 10:, Folder 444)
    - Special Ad Hoc Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 10:, Folder 445)
  - Subseries H: Meskill Policies, 1969-1975
    - Agency Budget requests, 1973 (Box 10:, Folder 446)
    - Auditors, 1973-1974 (Box 10:, Folder 447)
    - Auditors Fund Cut, 1973 (Box 10:, Folder 448)
    - Audit Review Committee, 1974 (Box 10:, Folder 449)
    - Budget, 1973 (Box 10:, Folder 450)
    - Budget results, 1974-1975 (Box 10:, Folder 451)
    - Budget results—Mental Health, 1971-1974 (Box 10:, Folder 452)
    - Civil Service Violations, 1973-1974 (Box 10:, Folder 453)
    - Cost of living—retired, 1971-1972 (Box 10:, Folder 454)
    - Deficit, 1973 (Box 10:, Folder 455)
    - DeMatteo and auditors, 1974 (Box 10:, Folder 456)
    - Democratic Budget—Tax cuts, 1973-1974 (Box 10:, Folder 457)
    - Democrats attack Republicans, 1973 (Box 10:, Folder 458)
    - Fiscal—Democratic State Campaign, 1974 (Box 10:, Folder 459)
    - Highway Fund, 1973 (Box 10:, Folder 460)
    - Inefficiency caused by budget cuts, 1974 (Box 10:, Folder 461)
    - Issues, 1974 465 (Box 10:, Folder 462)
    - Library Bill, 1974 (Box 10:, Folder 463)
    - Meskill
      - Average Daily Membership (ADM) Grants, 1974 (Box 10:, Folder 464)
      - Appointees, 1972-1974 (Box 10:, Folder 465)
      - Appointments—Names, 1973 (Box 10:, Folder 466)
      - Budget, 1972-1973 (Box 10:, Folder 467)
      - Budget, 1974-1975 (Box 10:, Folder 468)
      - Cities, 1971 (Box 10:, Folder 469)
      - Community Affairs, Department of, 1971-1974 (Box 10:, Folder 470)
      - Environmental Issues, 1974 (Box 10:, Folder 471)